aidpage.com 2016-11-25

# Privacy Policy - People Networks Inc.

  1. Our Commitment to Privacy
  2. The Information We Gather
  3. The Way We Use Information
  4. Third Party Services
  5. Data Security
  6. Privacy Policy Changes
  7. How To Contact Us

##### 1\. Our Commitment To Privacy

We, at People Networks, Inc. ("People Networks"), understand and care about the importance of your online privacy rights. Please, read this Privacy Policy statement, which describes what personally identifiable information ("PII") we collect from you and what we do or do not do in order to better protect it. The Privacy Policy deals strictly with what People Networks does with your PII submitted via listed here People Networks' services ("Services") and People Networks' websites ("Sites") only and does not deal with, or take responsibility of what others may do with your PII if you decide to publish any part of you personally identifiable information on any of the People Networks public or restricted Sites. This notice applies to all current Sites' visitors ("Visitors") and members ("Members") as well as former Visitors and Members of the Sites. If you have objections to the Privacy Policy, you should not access and use the Sites and Services. If you have questions or concerns about People Networks Privacy Policy, you can always contact us via mail sent to: Re: Privacy Policy, People Networks Inc., 16192 Coastal Hwy, Lewes, Delaware 19958, USA.

##### 2\. The Information We Gather

People Networks offers web services enabling people to publish various contents and communicate via various Services offered on or through the Sites. Any PII that is collected by People Networks is provided by you strictly on a voluntary basis. You can visit our Sites without providing any PII. However, if you would like to use our Services to submit, upload, post, display, contribute, transmit, otherwise make available on the Sites or publish (collectively, "Publish") information, text, graphics, sounds, messages, photos, music, video, links, software, data, profiles and content (collectively, "Content") you may have to register as a Member and create profile(s) by providing related PII. The information we collect in such cases is necessary to provide you with access to the Services and includes your name or nickname which is used for your profile creating. It is up to you to include any additional PII for your profile(s) on People Networks Sites such as your full name, gender, age, occupation / title, organization, email, website, country, state/province, city, preferred language(s) of communication or any other information you deem necessary to better define and/or make more personal your profile(s) on the Sites.

Persons under age of 13 are prohibited to use the Sites and Services and People Networks does not knowingly collect or monitor any information that may be Published by such persons. If People Networks learns that a profile is created and/or Content is Published by a person under age of 13, People Networks will immediately remove and delete that profile and Content from the Sites.

People Networks collects also information that is not considered PII such as your browser’s type and IP address. This information is gathered from all Visitors and Members using the Sites and Services.

Some of the information we ask you to provide on the Sites registration and profile forms and wizards is identified as mandatory (usually the fields are marked with an asterisk) and some is not mandatory. If you do not wish to provide valid data for the mandatory fields, you may not be able to engage in further activities or benefit from offered Services.

On some pages, you can submit information about other people - for example, if you would like to notify others about your Site space or page via email. In this case, the only type of information we may collect is the email address. 

People Networks Sites contain links to other websites, not owned, operated, or otherwise related to People Networks, at which PII may be collected. In such cases, the collection and use of your PII will be governed by the privacy policies applicable to those websites. 

To improve our Sites and Services and better serve our Members and Visitors, we may use "cookies". Cookies are simple text files stored on your computer by your Web browser. Cookies that may be created on your computer by using our websites do not contain personally identifiable information and do not compromise your privacy or security. They provide a method of distinguishing website users and enable us to record your preferences. Cookies cannot be executed as programs or deliver viruses. Most browsers are set by default to accept cookies. You can set up your browser to not accept cookies. In such case, however, you may not be able to access some of our pages and use some of our Services.

This notice applies to all personally identifiable information submitted to and collected on the listed above Sites only, which includes but is not limited to member registration, profile creating, submitting parts or complete PII via the Services to various registration and profile forms and wizards, emails, and forms and documents received by mail or fax. 

##### 3\. The Way We Use Information

While information we collect is the foundation of our ability to provide you with superior products and services, our most important asset is our users’ trust. Keeping our users’ information secure and using it only as promised is a top priority for all of us at People Networks.

We use the PII as you provide it to support and enhance the main functionality of Sites and Services.

We use the name or nickname you provide when register as a Member only to allow you access to People Networks Sites and Services. People Networks does not sell, rent, share, trade or give away your registration name or nickname.

Your profile information that may include name, gender, age, occupation / title, organization, email, website, country, state/province, city and preferred language(s) of communication and which is provided at your discretion is always automatically displayed and visible to the visitors on your home page. People Networks does not take responsibility of what third parties may do with your publicly Published profile information. People Networks itself does not sell, rent, share or trade your profile information.

We may use your return email address to answer abuse reports, or suggestions we receive. Such email addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. 

We may disclose personal information, when required by the law, in order to comply with the law or regulations of a government agency, or regulatory body, or in response to a subpoena, warrant, court order or other legal process. We may disclose account or registration information when we have reason to believe that disclosing such information is necessary to identify, contact and bring legal action against someone who may be violating our Terms of Service Agreement, including Code of Conduct, in order to protect data security of our customers and our intellectual property. 

The information that is considered as non personally identifiable is used only in aggregated way for statistical purposes and analysis and never used in a way that may personally identify you.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

##### 4\. Third Party Services

On some of the Sites, People Networks may use third party services for the purpose of serving and/or targeting of ads, promotions and other marketing messages. In order to perform their services, such third parties normally collect anonymous data through the use of cookies. Specifically, we use Google's services. Google, as a third party service, uses cookies to serve ads on our sites. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visits to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

##### 5\. Data Security

Since no data transmitted over Internet or stored on Internet servers can be guaranteed to be absolutely secure, People Networks cannot ensure or warrant the security of any personally identifiable information you are transmitting to the Sites or posting it on non-public (restricted or private) pages. You understand and acknowledge that the submission of any such information by you via the Internet or posting it on non-public (restricted or private) pages is at our own risk. Once People Networks receives your information it makes efforts to ensure its security on its platform and Sites. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, People Networks maintains appropriate physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards. 

##### 6\. Privacy Policy Changes

People Networks reserves the right to change its Privacy Policy at its sole discretion. In such cases, the Privacy Policy posted on our Sites will be updated accordingly. 

In case People Networks sells its assets to another entity or is acquired or merged with another entity, Member information generally is one of the transferred business assets. In such cases, transferred customer information remains subject to the pre-existing Privacy Policy, and the new entity is required to advise you on any Privacy Policy changes.

##### 7\. How to Contact Us

Should you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please write us at:

People Networks Inc.  
9577 Big Man St  
Las Vegas, NV 89123

© 2007-2015 People Networks. All Rights Reserved.
